(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 1,
"subtitles": 2
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
BIRDS NIGHT OUT - Pavolia Reine Birthday 2024 -
With Announcement!
BIRDS NIGHT OUT
Pavolia Reine Birthday 2024
START 2024.09.09 20:00 WIB / 22:00 JST
Peh, peh, peh, peh...
Wait, it's not even started yet.
Hello! Hello world!
Meron ba tao? Tes, tes...
Is anyone there? Test, test...
With Announcement!
Don't look away from me now
Kiss me
Love me
In the night
Kiss me
Love me
Five, four, three, two, one, zero...
I don't think I'll be able to get you off my mind
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
Dancing in the moonlight, oh
Don't look away from me now
Nah, nah-nah-nah-nah-nah-nah, Ready for my show
Okay, たちまち独壇場 Listen, listen
Okay, instantly it's a one-woman show, listen, listen
Nah, nah-nah-nah-nah-nah-nah, Ready for my show
Okay! 傾け！
Okay! Let's get wild!
振り回そう
Let's swing it around
Ya-ya-ya-ya Showtime
天辺の鳴り渡る御我 おいで
I am the one echoing at the summit, come here
宵をコンプリート オーライ
Complete the night, alright
Hell yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
ジャンジャンノリノリで超簡単
Rocking out non-stop, it's super easy
Brah, brah, brah, pow!
Ain't nobody stop
全土絢爛豪華
Dazzling and gorgeous across the entire land
Attention 騒ごうか
Attention, shall we make some noise?
敗走児にも 畜生道的 意思表示に
Even for the losers, a beast-like expression of will
もうじき衝撃の声 高らかに 堂々と Bang
Soon, a shocking voice, loud and proud, Bang!
もう銀河は 疾っくの疾っくの淘汰
The galaxy was weeded out long, long ago
Hey繚乱 豪華絢爛 お出ましだ
Hey, in full bloom, grand and luxurious, I have arrived!
格好つけてるつもりは No, no
I'm not trying to act cool, no, no
つもりは
I intended to...
オートマティックに
automatically
溢れちゃう本能
overflowing instinct
宣う断頭台の上で
proclaiming on the guillotine
燥げ華麗
frolic magnificently
Ratatata warning
Nah-nah-ready for my show
万歳 遊ぶ気に
Banzai, feeling like playing
トドメ刺しちゃえ Shout it out, shout it out
Give the finishing blow, shout it out, shout it out
Nah-nah-ready for my show
はんなり勘通りに八艘飛び Shout it out, shout it out
Gracefully leaping across eight ships as expected, shout it out
Look at me now
皮膚を破りそうな程に跳ねる心臓
A heart bouncing enough to tear the skin
くらい激情的 真相
so passionate, the truth
Eeny, meeny, miny, moe からの御来光
Eeny, meeny, miny, moe, sunrise from the shell
かくれんぼしてるその気持ち解放
Release that feeling that is playing hide and seek
理性アディオス
Reason, adios
しゃかりきに躍っちゃえ
Dance enthusiastically
蛇腹蛇尾 騙る二枚刃 嫉妬するようなジュース
Serpentine tail, deceitful double-edged blade, jealous juice
たぶらかすな カットなっちゃえ
Don't deceive, just cut it
カルマに至る前に揺蕩うわ
Wavering before reaching karma
嫌々 十色のバタフライ
Reluctantly, a ten-colored butterfly
No escape
ご存じの通り 騒々しい鼓動に
As you know, to the noisy heartbeat
絆されても止まれない
Even if bound, I can't stop
衝動に塗装し
Coating the impulse
描いたDaybreak
The painted daybreak
肺貫通低音狂
Lung-piercing bass craze
Nah-nah-ready for my show
異例の危険度 比類なき活気充満
Unprecedented risk, filled with unparalleled energy
Nah-nah-ready for my show
一気呵成 嗚呼！
In one stroke, ah!
Nah-nah-ready for my show
万歳 遊ぶ気にトドメ刺しちゃえ Shout it out, shout it out
Banzai, give the finishing blow to the feeling of playing, shout it out
Nah-nah-ready for my show
巻き起こすために Slay, slay, slay, slay
To stir it up, slay, slay, slay, slay
一切合切忘れて Shout it out
Forget everything and shout it out
右に左まとめて
Altogether to the right and left
Pull up, 思い切り Clap, clap, clap
Pull up, as much as you can, clap, clap, clap
なにはともあれ合縁奇縁 Shout it out, shout it out
Anyway, a strange turn of fate, shout it out, shout it out
チート, gifted, 荒技 wanted, 禁忌, 禁じ手, 明らかに以て
Cheat, gifted, rough technique wanted, taboo, forbidden move, clearly with
反則, 異次元, この世のもんではないです。無理ゲー, それ聞いてないて
Foul, different dimension, not of this world. Impossible game, I didn't hear that
エイ, ライバル口を揃えて、エイ, ライバル口を揃えて
Ay, rivals speaking in unison, ay, rivals speaking in unison
バグで, マグレ, 認めねーゼッテー。マジで？これおま...全部生身で？
Bug, fluke, definitely won't admit it. Seriously? Is this you... all with just your body?
It's not me, it's not me, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Bling-bang-bang, bling-bang-bang, bling-bang-bang-born...
実力を発揮し切る前に相手の方がバックれてくらしい
Seems the opponent runs away before I can show my full strength
上がり切るハードル, very happy, 明らかにダントツ出来返し
Rising hurdles, very happy, clearly an outstanding result
相変わらず脱皮してる毎日
Every day I'm still shedding my skin
Bling, 誰の七光りも要らない、お前のICより熱い俺の
Bling, don't need anyone's influence, mine's hotter than your IC
パッと見出来なさそうな事ばかりだけど
Lots of things that look impossible at first glance, but...
あ、キレてる、呆れてる周り、恵まれてる家族友達
Ah, they're mad, they're fed up around me, blessed with family and friends
もう反則的立ち位置、取れて任せときゃ良い
Already in a foul position, just take it and leave it to me
教科書に無い、問題集に無い、超BADな呪い
Not in textbooks, not in problem sets, a super BAD curse
鏡よ鏡、答えちゃって
Mirror mirror, answer me
Who's the best? I'm the best! Oh yeah!
生身のまま行けるところまで, To the next, to the 1番上
Going as far as I can with just my body, To the next, to the very top
Bling-bang-bang, bling-bang-bang, bling-bang-bang-born...
Ey-day 俺のままで居るだけで超 flex
Ey-day, just being myself is super flex
Ey-day 誰も口を挟めない don't test
Ey-day, no one can interject, don't test
Ey-day 俺のままで居るだけで超 flex
Ey-day, just being myself is super flex
Ey-day 誰も口を挟めない don't test
Ey-day, no one can interject, don't test
学歴も無い、前科も無い、余裕でBling Bling
No education, no criminal record, comfortably Bling Bling
この存在自体が文化財なの、脳みそBling Bling
This existence itself is a cultural asset, brain Bling Bling
高級車は買える、免許は無い、愛車はGreen
Can buy luxury cars, no license, my car is Green
全国各地揺らす逸品、このベルがBling Bling
A masterpiece shaking the whole country, this bell is Bling Bling
パレットなら満タン、関西訛り生身の言霊
Palette is full, Kansai dialect, the spirit of language in the flesh
音楽、幸運、勝利の女神、今も三叉路
Music, luck, the goddess of victory, still at a crossroads
漫画みたいなエグい奴等と、まんま張り合えてしまってる漫画
A manga where I'm competing exactly with nasty guys like in a manga
圧倒的チカラ、この頭と口から
Overwhelming power, from this head and mouth
この身体 tattoo は入って無い、このツラに傷も付いて無い
No tattoos on this body, no scars on this face
繰り返しやらしてく、レベチ違い、イカつい年輪も刻ましまわ
Keep doing it repeatedly, a different level, carving out tough tree rings too
Bling-bang-bang, bling-bang-bang, bling-bang-bang-born...
俺のままでBlingして、Bounceして、Bounceして、飛び上がるためにBorn、敵陣にポン
Bling as myself, bounce, bounce, born to leap up, pop into enemy territory
鏡よ鏡、答えちゃって
Mirror mirror, answer me
Who's the best? I'm the best! Oh yeah!
生身のまま行けるところまで, To the next, to the 1番上
Going as far as I can with just my body, To the next, to the very top
Bling-bang-bang, bling-bang-bang, bling-bang-bang-born...
Ey-day 俺のままで居るだけで超 flex
Ey-day, just being myself is super flex
Ey-day 誰も口を挟めない don't test
Ey-day, no one can interject, don't test
Ey-day 俺のままで居るだけで超 flex
Ey-day, just being myself is super flex
居るだけでチョックス
Just by being here, Chocks
エイエイ
Ay ay
誰も口を挟ませない
Won't let anyone get a word in
Kiss me!
Keep those lips from wandering off
Tell me every sweet and tender thought!
Give me all you have to give and more...
Fantasy's where futures are born!
Can you feel the beat?
The rhythm, the tune...
Your heart and mine - the countdown...
If you feel something coming to you,
Believe it and scream it aloud!
I don't think I'll miss you anymore
like I did the day you left.
There's so many just like you I could use instead!
'Cause passion burning bright only hurts you in the end.
This city will swallow the pain...
Tomorrow's another today...
Curtain call at dawn, darling! SHOWTIME!
Spend our moment dancing in the MOONLIGHT!
'Til your gaze starts swaying with my body...
Keep your eyes on me!
Take me somewhere deep into the night...
Touch me - here, there, anywhere you like!
Trust me! Won't you let me look inside?
Fantasies and futures collide...
It's just the two of us beneath the starry sky...
If the only way to keep on living is "Keep on living strong!"
Then you can keep the kindness 'cause I'm moving on!
No need to say goodbye to me - I'm already gone!
Just wipe all your tears away
And know we'll start over someday...
All your heart, your soul, your body...
You belong to one and only!
Unconditionally yearning,
Knowing no one else will do...
Can you feel the bond between us grow tight?
We're closer than we've ever been!
Follow me! Match your rhythm to mine,
And let it all out from within!
I don't think I miss you anymore
than I did the day you left.
I won't say "I love you." I know I'll take it back!
I'm used to this, I'm not the same old loser that
Burned bright and quick, where candles and wind could never last!
A city that's living in fast-forward's
The perfect place for lovers like us to take a chance!
There's nothing here to stop us when in Rome, romance!
And I won't let you leave me alone without a dance!
I don't wanna' hear a goodbye...
Don't break the illusion tonight...
Curtain call at dawn, darling! SHOWTIME!
Spend forever living 'til the SUNRISE!
Feel that look, even with the lights off,
Dance until we drop!
Wow! Hello everybody!
This is my,
my very, very first 3D live concert!
What do you think about it so far?
And this is the hashtag #ReineMeptember2024, so Reine and...
...pep-pep-pep-pep! You know the sound I make?
...September, and this year, 2024.
Easy to remember, right?
So I'm looking forward to your posts and your thoughts,
you know what you think about it on X, okay?
Please do post a lot, I will be looking!
And so, the idea behind this live event today is Rave.
今回のライブのコンセプトは、RAVEです。
The concept for this live performance is Rave.
I want you to see a cool side of me, ね？
I want you to see a cool side of me, right?
もっと、あの、かっこいい私を...
More of, you know, a cool me...
普段はスーパーエレガントですね、スーパーエレガント。
Usually I'm super elegant, super elegant.
エレガント、エレガント banget gitu.
Elegant, really elegant.
Aku kan biasanya elegant gitu.
I'm usually elegant like that.
Tapi jadi sekarang tuh pengennya tuh yang
'oh aku mau mengasih lihat yang keren' gitu.
But now, I want to show a "cool" side.
Ya pokoknya gitu deh, ya gini lah.
Well, it's like that.
Terus kayak di atas tuh ada mirror ball!
And then, there's a mirror ball up there!
Keren banget!
It's so cool!
Jadi tuh pokoknya rave banget. It's so rave-boy!
It's such a rave vibe. It's so rave-boy!
And there's so many planets.
Keren kan? Keren kan? Keren gak sih? Keren gak sih?
Cool, right? Cool, right? Isn't it cool? Isn't it cool?
And then, there's lasers as well.
You guys saw, right?
Yeah, bola disko mantap!
Yeah, the disco ball is awesome!
Terus ada juga... there's also
audio spectrum everywhere!
And also... there's also
You guys saw it, right?
Did anyone here notice?
During the performance?
Well they're not here right now though.
The audio spectrums, they move in sync with the music.
For those who didn't notice,
I hope you pay attention to them
in the upcoming songs, okay?
Yeah, it's super cool.
Eh ya gitu deh, pokoknya keren banget.
Yeah, like that. It's really cool.
Ada warnanya biru. Jadi ini biasanya tuh biru...
There's blue. It's usually blue...
Kayaknya sekarang biru...
It looks blue now...
Tapi bisa warna-warni sesuai lagu.
But it can be colorful depending on the song.
Aku juga udah siapin setlist dengan lagu-lagu
yang asyik banget buat joget...
I've also prepared a setlist with songs
that are fun to dance to...
Biar cocok sama vibe rave-nya ne.
To match the rave vibe.
Pokoknya the songs are very, very rave-boy deh.
Anyway, the songs are very, very rave-boy.
And then... apa ya?
And then... what else?
And then, the songs I sang...
It was 'Show', 'Bling-Bang-Bang-Born'.
I had the hat on, but I don't have it anymore,
but yeah, I had them on.
And then if you missed it, well sorry,
They were bangers so please do check out the archive.
And also for 'Illusion Night',
Well it's 'Illusion Night',
You know 'Illusion Night'.
For those of you who don't know,
stream 'Illusion Night', okay?
And up next, we have many, many guests
Making appearances so please, please, please
look forward to it, okay?
Abis ini bakal ada banyak tamu yang tampil.
After this, there will be many guests appearing.
Jadi nantikan terus, oke?
So please stay tuned, okay?
But, before we go to the next song,
I will take a moment to get ready, okay?
Ganti baju dulu guys.
Changing clothes first, guys.
Aku mau ganti baju.
I want to change my clothes.
Ganti baju, ganti baju, ganti baju.
Changing clothes, changing clothes, changing clothes.
DADDY ! DADDY ! DO ! Lyrics, Music: 水野良樹
DADDY ! DADDY ! DO ! Lyrics, Music: Yoshiki Mizuno
DADDY ! DADDY ! DO ! 欲しいのさ
DADDY ! DADDY ! DO ! I want it
あなたのすべてが
All of you
愛に抱かれ ギラギラ 燃えてしまいたい
Embraced by love, I want to burn brilliantly
可愛げな KISS で 1, 2, 3
With a cute kiss, 1, 2, 3
目線そらして ズルいよね
Turning your eyes away, that's unfair
火照り出す 僕の気持ち
My feelings start to flush
もてあそぶみたいで
It's like you're toying with me
追いかけちゃ だめなのは
I know I shouldn't chase you
わかってる でも無理さ
I know, but it's impossible
一度踏み出せば 戻れなくて
Once I take a step forward, I can't go back
仮面は脱ぎ捨てて
Throw away the mask
いけない 言葉で
With forbidden words
遊びが本気になる
The play becomes serious
DADDY ! DADDY ! DO ! 欲しいのさ
DADDY ! DADDY ! DO ! I want it
あなたのすべてが
All of you
騙されたら それでもいい
If I'm deceived, that's fine too
もっと震わせて 魅せてくれ
Make me tremble more, show me
僕だけに 笑顔の裏まで
To only me, even behind your smile
愛に抱かれ ギラギラ 燃えてしまいたい
Embraced by love, I want to burn brilliantly
躊躇など しない No No No
I won't hesitate, no no no
二度と逢えない ひとだから
Because you're someone I'll never meet again
後悔に 触れるのなら
If I'm going to feel regret
恋の火に 焼かれたい
I want to be burned by the fire of love
わざとでしょう 流し目が
Your sidelong glance must be intentional
愛しさを 刺激する
It stimulates my affection
そっと振り返る 美しさに
Turning back gently, at your beauty
心はつかまれて
My heart is captured
呼吸が 止まって
My breathing stops
遊びが本気になる
The play becomes serious
DADDY ! DADDY ! DO ! ぶつけたい
DADDY ! DADDY ! DO ! I want to strike
想いのすべてを
All of my feelings
綺麗なもの だけじゃなくて
Not just the beautiful things
危険な願いも
But dangerous wishes too
止めないで その声が 僕を連れていく
Don't stop, that voice leads me away
愛に抱かれ ギラギラ 燃えてしまいたい
Embraced by love, I want to burn brilliantly
燃えてしまいたい
I want to burn away
「あなただけ」と言うくちびるが
The lips that say "only you"
優しく微笑むたび
Every time they smile gently
飲み込まれて
I'm swallowed up
いざなわれて
I'm lured in
未知の世界
An unknown world
触れて
Touching it
OH OH
最後まで　あなたにゆだねて
Entrusting myself to you until the end
壊れるならそれでもいい
If I break, that's fine too
もっと狂わせて
Drive me more crazy
魅せてくれ　僕だけに
Enchant me, only for me
こころの奥まで
To the depths of my heart
愛に抱かれ
Embraced by love
ギラギラ燃えたい
I want to burn brightly
いのち果てる夜明けまで
Until the dawn when life ends
PaIII.SENSATION
暫く暮れて眠れる日々も
The days when I could sleep after dark
今夜辺りサヨナラできる気がする
I feel like I can say goodbye tonight
胸の昂り見透かされたい
I want my heart's excitement to be seen through
嬉し知らずの気持ち隠しても
Even if I hide my feelings of unknown joy
既に遅いわ夜も連れ
It's already too late, take the night with you
今から全てで飛ばしてあげる
I'll send everything flying from now on
センセーション
Sensation
愛想振る舞いに
In my pleasant behavior
センセーション
Sensation
巻き起こすのよ
I'm going to stir it up
センセーション
Sensation
どこ吹く風も
Whatever the wind blows
未体験を通り越して
Go beyond the unexperienced
センセーション
Sensation
なんて素敵な
How wonderful
熱情感　満ち溢れてく
The feeling of passion overflows
私
I
何者も
No one else
どうでもいいから　ほらその手で
It doesn't matter, look, with that hand
深くへ
Into the depths
ごまかさなくても愛しているわ
I love you even without deception
センセーション
Sensation
愛想振る舞いに
In my pleasant behavior
センセーション
Sensation
巻き起こすのよ
I'm going to stir it up
センセーション
Sensation
どこ吹く風も
Whatever the wind blows
未体験を通り越して
Go beyond the unexperienced
センセーション
Sensation
なんて素敵な
How wonderful
熱情感　満ち溢れてく
The feeling of passion overflows
私
I
何者も
No one else
どうでもいいから　ほらその手で
It doesn't matter, look, with that hand
深くへ　合図も無く
Into the depths, without a signal
Waaah! That was two more songs!
2曲歌いました。いかがだったでしょうか？
I sang two songs. How did you like them?
Hehe. The first song I sang, "DADDY! DADDY! DO!"
together with a very, very special guest called Reine Bogel!
可愛かったでしょう？ Reine Bogel.
Wasn't she cute? Reine Bogel.
Lucu ya? Ih gemoy kenyal-kenyal unyu pengen uh gitu lho!
Cute right? Oh so squishy and adorable, I just want to—you know!
I would want one Reine Bogel in my home. You would want one too, right?
And then... ya gitu deh. Pokoknya for this song, I've always wanted to sing this song...
And then... yeah. Anyway, for this song, I've always wanted to sing this song...
...in like an official live, and I finally can do it. So I'm very happy, happy, happy about it!
And for the second song, I sang... apa ya? Wait, it's...
And for the second song, I sang... what was it? Wait, it's...
"PaIII.SENSATION"! Yes, I did it! It's such a long title, but a very, very beautiful song.
I personally invited other Holo members...
We have senpais and not senpais,
we have Lui, we have Kanata-senpai,
we have Wawa Kiara and me together.
Heh! Reine! Heh!
Kenapa nggak panggil aku emak sih?
Why didn't you call me 'mom'?
Makasih, makasih semuaku,
Thank you, thank you my everything,
kita kan teman.
we are friends after all.
Mau apa sih?
What do you want?
Lupa ya?
Did you forget?
Yo, who taught you that?
Kikiniki, I taught it myself because I'm from Hololive Indonesia.
Amayo! Amayo!
Is it so? Is it so?
Emang iya? Emang iya? Really?
Is that so? Is that so? Really?
And I have no memo in my head. No, no, no. Secret, secret memo.
Secret, secret memo.
Iya, Hololive Indonesia banget sih guys,
Yeah, it's very Hololive Indonesia, guys,
menurut aku, ya, Hololive Indonesia.
in my opinion, yeah, Hololive Indonesia.
So, okay, well...
I don't know if it's okay for her to be here. Is she... is it okay?
Yes, sure!
Really?
Tanjak, tanjak, tanjak, tanjak...
Ya udah deh, ya udah deh. Oke, oke. Wah.
Alright then, alright then. Okay, okay. Wow.
Well, okay, well, since she's here anyway, so, what'd you think about the song?
I always love your song choices.
I feel you're a genius of putting the right people together with the right song.
'Cause I also really love your Bitter Choco Decoration cover that you did a long time ago.
I always listen to it. Every single week.
Yeah, and now you get to do a mature, cool song.
I've always wanted to do it, you know, with like...
ooh, four people, you know? Spicy, right?
Very spicy!
Always spicy! Always, always spicy, spicy.
Did you guys miss Pavonashi?
Ooh, Pavonashi!
Yeah, this is... we've been together so many times now.
I know, I was in your live last time, right? My birthday.
And I was first in your 3D debut.
Oh, oh, oh! We also sang a spicy song then.
Yeah! Spicy!
That's the spicy tradition. Let's go! Keep it going!
We like it spicy.
Well, I like it sweet, but, you know.
This is sweet and spicy, it's a good combo, right? Yay!
Oke, terus apa lagi? Kita harus ngomong apa lagi nih?
Okay, what else? What else should we say?
What shall we say?
Hmm. I want to do... our bird mating dance!
Okay, okay, okay, we can do that!
Yeah, yeah, yeah! It's been a long time.
Do you guys know the OG Pavonashi lore?
Do you remember it? Do you remember it?
Do it with us!
Yes! Do it with us! Bird mating dance!
Yeah, okay. So I... okay, okay.
Reine, apa?
Reine, what?
Happy Birthday!
Thank you, Takanashi-senpai! I was gonna make a bet if she's gonna forget or not!
Whoa! Piko piko! Piko piko!
Bye bye, Happy Birthday!
Oh, okay, bye-bye!
Makasih! Thank you banget Kiara ya udah datang, guys!
Thank you! Thank you so much Kiara for coming, guys!
Thank you so much, even though she's not supposed to be here.
Thank you so much Kiara for coming!
And next up we still have more songs
and more guests. That's right, you heard it right,
so please stay tuned for the next song.
無敵の笑顔で荒らすメディア
A media stir with an invincible smile
知りたいその秘密ミステリアス
I want to know your secret, so mysterious
抜けてるとこさえ彼女のエリア
Even her flaws are within her area
完璧で嘘つきな君は
You, perfect and a liar,
天才的なアイドル様
are a genius idol
今日何食べた？好きな本は？
What did you eat today? What's your favorite book?
遊びに行くならどこに行くの？
If you go out, where do you go?
何も食べてない、それは内緒
I haven't eaten anything, that's a secret
何を聞かれてものらりくらり
No matter what I'm asked, I dodge it smoothly
そう淡々とだけど燦々と
So indifferently, yet brilliantly
見えそうで見えない蜜の味
A taste of honey that's almost visible but not
ないないない、それもないないない
No, no, no, none of that either
好きなタイプは？相手は？さあ答えて
What's your type? Who's your partner? Come on, answer
誰かを好きになることなんて私分からなくてさ
I don't really understand things like falling in love with someone
嘘か本当か知り得ないそんな言葉にまた一人堕ちる
With words that might be lies or truth, someone falls for them again
また好きにさせる
Making them love you again
誰もが目を奪われていく君は完璧で究極のアイドル
Everyone is captivated by you, you're the perfect, ultimate idol
金輪際現れない一番星の生まれ変わり
A miracle that will never appear again, the reincarnation of the brightest star
その笑顔で愛してるで誰も彼も虜にしていく
With that smile and "I love you", you captivate everyone
その瞳がその言葉が嘘でもそれは完全なアイ
Even if those eyes and those words are lies, it's a perfect love
はいはいあの子は特別です我々は端からおまけです
Yes, yes, that girl is special. We've been just extras from the start
お星様の引き立て役Ｂです
We're just the background character B to make the star shine
全てがあの子のお陰なわけない
There's no way everything is thanks to her
洒落臭い妬み嫉妬なんてないわけない
Cheeky envy and jealousy? There's no way we don't have them
これはネタじゃないからこそ許せない
This isn't a joke, that's why it's unforgivable
完璧じゃない君じゃ許せない自分を許せない
I won't forgive you if you're not perfect. I won't forgive myself
誰よりも強い君以外は認めない
I won't recognize anyone but you, who are stronger than anyone
誰もが信じ崇めてるまさに最強で無敵のアイドル
Everyone believes and worships you, truly the strongest, invincible idol
弱点なんて見当たらない一番星を宿してる
No weaknesses to be found, harboring the brightest star
弱いとこなんて見せちゃダメダメ
You mustn't show any weak points
知りたいくないとこは見せずに
Without showing the parts people don't want to see
唯一無二じゃなくちゃイヤイヤそれこそ本物の愛
You must be one of a kind. That's what true love is
それこそ本物の愛
That is what true love is
もっと笑顔で沸かすメディア
Thrilling the media with even more smiles
隠し切るこの秘密だけは
Except for this one secret to be kept hidden
愛してるって嘘で積むキャリア
A career built on the lie of "I love you"
これこそ私なりの愛だ
This is my own way of loving
流れる汗も綺麗なアクア
Even the flowing sweat is a beautiful aqua
ルビーを隠したこの瞼
These eyelids that hide rubies
歌い踊り舞う私はマリア
Singing and dancing, I am Maria
そう嘘はとびきりの愛だ
Yes, lies are the greatest love
誰かに愛されたことも
Neither having been loved by someone
誰かのこと愛したことも
Nor having ever loved someone
ないそんな私の嘘が
That lie of mine, who has never...
いつか本当になること
...one day coming true
信じてる
I believe in it
いつかきっと全部手に入れる
One day, I'll surely have it all
私はそう欲張りなアイドル
I'm such a greedy idol
等身大でみんなのこと
Exactly as I am,
ちゃんと愛したいから
Because I want to love you all truly
今日も嘘をつくの
I'll tell lies again today
この言葉がいつか本当になる日を願って
Praying for the day these words come true
それでもまだ
Even so,
君にだけは言えずにいたけど
I still haven't been able to say it only to you
やっと言えた
I finally said it
これは絶対嘘じゃない
This is definitely not a lie
愛してる
I love you
どうでもいいような夜だけど
Though it's a night that doesn't really matter
響めき煌めきと君も
The resonance and the sparkle, and you too
まだ止まった刻む針も
Even the ticking hands that have stopped
入り混じった散らかる部屋も
Even the cluttered room where things are all mixed up
変わらないね 思い出しては二人
It doesn't change, does it? Remembering, the two of us
歳を重ねてた
Grew older together
また止まった落とす針を
The needle that dropped and stopped again
よく流した聞き飽きるほど
I played it often, until I grew tired of it
変わらないね 変わらないで
It doesn't change, please don't change
いられたのは君だけか
Was it only you who could stay that way?
無鉄砲で はぐらかして
Being reckless, being evasive
触れた先をためらうように
As if hesitating at what I touched
足踏みして ズレた針を余所に
Pacing, ignoring the needle that's out of sync
揃い始めた 息が
Our breaths began to align
どうでもいいような夜だけど
Though it's a night that doesn't really matter
響めき煌めきと君も
The resonance and the sparkle, and you too
踊ろう
Let's dance
どうでもいいような夜だけど
Though it's a night that doesn't really matter
二人刻もう
Let's keep time together
透き通った白い肌も
Even that transparent white skin
その笑った無邪気な顔も
Even that smiling innocent face
変わらないね 変わらないで
It doesn't change, please don't change
いられるのは今だけか
Is it only now that we can stay this way?
見つめるほどに 溢れるメモリー
The more I look, the more memories overflow
浮つく心に コーヒーを
Coffee for my flighty heart
乱れた髪に かすれたメロディー
A raspy melody for my messy hair
混ざり合ってよう もう一度
Let's blend together once more
どうでもいいような夜だけど
Though it's a night that doesn't really matter
煌めき色の君と
With you, colored in sparkles
踊ろう
Let's dance
どうでもいいような夜だけど
Though it's a night that doesn't really matter
二人刻もう
Let's keep time together
夜は長い おぼつかない
The night is long, uncertain
今にも止まりそうな ミュージック
Music that sounds like it might stop any second
君といたい 溺れてたい
I want to be with you, I want to drown
明日が来なくたって もういいの
Even if tomorrow never comes, it's okay
どうでもいいような夜だけど
Though it's a night that doesn't really matter
響めき煌めきと君も
The resonance and the sparkle, and you too
踊ろう
Let's dance
どうでもいいような夜だけど
Though it's a night that doesn't really matter
愛して
Love me
どうでもいいから 僕だけを
It doesn't matter, just [look at] me
ふらつきよろめきながらも
Even while staggering and stumbling
踊ろう
Let's dance
どうでもいいような夜だけど
Though it's a night that doesn't really matter
二人刻もう
Let's keep time together
Let's etch it together
Yay!
I hope you enjoyed those two songs!
Tadi kita udah dengerin dua lagu lagi ya!
We just heard two more songs!
Wow, untuk yang pertama, tamu untuk lagu ini...
Wow, for the first one, the guest for this song...
Lagu apa tuh? "Idol"...
What song was that? "Idol"...
...adalah Kobo!
...is Kobo!
Jadi kenapa sih pengen nyanyi sama Kobo?
Why do I want to sing with Kobo ya?
So, why did I want to sing with Kobo?
Why do I want to sing with Kobo?
Soalnya tuh kebetulan... e...
anak kecil ini di-drop...
Because it just so happens... that
this little kid was dropped...
...gitu di depan rumah Tante.
Jadi Tante mengajak dia deh...
...off in front of Auntie's house.
So Auntie invited her...
...selagi babysitting sambil diajak nyanyi aja gitu.
...to sing along while I was babysitting her.
I wanted to sing with her because, I don't know,
I just felt like... apa ya?
I just felt like... how should I say it?
Umm, she was dropped off in front of my door,
so I thought it would be nice to, you know,
babysit while singing with her, I guess.
And yeah, I thought this song fits
both our voice very well,
and we're both blue, you know, it's kind of like
the tall blue and the tiny blue,
so it all, it all makes sense. It's nice, right?
I hope you guys enjoyed our performance. Yeah!
And for "Night Dancer", our guest is Calliope!
It's Calli!
Calli is someone I've always admired.
She has such a cool voice,
such strong, elegant... I don't know how to say it,
but just, you know, very cool.
Very cool person, very cool vocals.
And this time I wanted to sing something
more chill and elegant...
Not elegant, chill, chill with her.
How was our, how was our dance?
I think, uh, both of us has, you know,
different individual styles,
and it's really interesting to see them
together in a performance.
And then, next up is the...
Did anybody guess it?
It's a DJ segment!
次はなんと、DJパートです！
Next is actually a DJ segment!
I'm going to be changing outfits
because I think, I don't know,
maybe if we're going to DJ, maybe we, we need
something more, you know,
more fit for DJ-ing kan bajunya ya?
more fit for DJ-ing, since this outfit isn't, right?
Okay, so I'm going to get changed. Okay?
See you soon!
星が揺らいで　夢を見ている
The stars are swaying, I'm dreaming
焦がれたその音を待ってるの
I'm waiting for that sound I've longed for
煌めく空　決めてる日々に
In the days I've decided under the sparkling sky
届けるこのメロディ
I'll deliver this melody
まだかな　覗いた
Is it time yet? I peeked
雨の降る街並みを弾ける音
The sound of rain popping in the streets
ポケットに詰め込んで
Stuffing it into my pocket
さあ　さあ！
Now, now!
君の好きな　ちょっとクールなデコパッパ
Your favorite, slightly cool dekopappa
秘密のステップに乗せて
Moving to a secret step
魔法のような　もっとビビッドなファッションショー
A magic-like, even more vivid fashion show
ライトが私を照らしてる
The lights are shining on me
星を追いて　夢を描くよ
Chasing the stars, drawing my dreams
焦がれたその声が呼んでるの
That voice I've longed for is calling me
煌めく空　迷うときも君に
Even when I'm lost under the sparkling sky
届けるこのメロディ
I'll deliver this melody to you
このままじゃ終われない
I can't let it end like this
特別なステージ　踊り明かそう
On this special stage, let's dance the night away
このままじっとしてられない
I can't just stand still
動き出そうよ　明日は晴れるから
Let's start moving, because tomorrow will be sunny
明日は晴れるから
Because tomorrow will be sunny
退屈な日常　このままでいいの？
Is this boring daily life okay as it is?
うつむいて携帯見てばかりで
Just looking down at my phone all the time
ハート止まっていても　心震わせたいの
Even if my heart stops, I want to make it tremble
これからが勝負　歩き出して行こうか
The real challenge starts now, let's start walking
1, 2, 3 で　星を見つけて
Find the stars on 1, 2, 3
4, 5, 6 で　君を見つけたの
I found you on 4, 5, 6
7, 8, 9 で　夢を見て...
Dreaming on 7, 8, 9...
見つめて Night out tonight まぶたが開くの
Staring, Night out tonight, my eyelids open.
次々身体に浴びせて You and me
Shower my body with it one after another, You and me.
次々頭にどっか贈るわ You and me
Sending it somewhere to my head one after another, You and me.
次々脳内にハッピーになれるの
One after another in my brain, I can become happy.
ドキドキ脳内に
My heart is pounding in my brain.
Are you ready?
Jollie Jollie night 止まることなんてないの
Jollie Jollie night, there's no stopping.
Shiny time is now 煌めいてこの舞台
Shiny time is now, sparkling on this stage.
Crazy crazy dance 心躍るよな予感
Crazy crazy dance, a feeling like my heart is dancing.
見つけたら特別な場所
When you find it, it's a special place.
Hey Jollie Jollie night Let's crazy party night
Stay up all night long Jollie Jollie Jollie yeah
Stay up all night long Music party night
Hey Jollie Jollie night Let's crazy party night
Stay up all night long Jollie Jollie Jollie yeah
たとえば君が私の意志を制御しようとも
Even if you, for example, try to control my will,
貌なき宣戦 望みもしない兵隊を投げる
a faceless declaration of war, throwing unwanted soldiers.
知らない空の下この異物がゆるめなく
Under an unknown sky, this foreign body will not loosen,
生まれ出づるこの不徳に生を奪われるまで
until my life is taken by this born immorality.
小窓の向こうに 日を重ね折紙付き
Beyond the small window, days pile up, certified.
残酷なほど咲く 張り詰めた収まる肺 声を聴け
Cruelly blooming, the tense, settled lungs, hear the voice.
私が真の刃と成った 既成概念を切って
I became the true blade, cutting through preconceived notions.
唱えて路を占める 差し支えなく 愛想もなく
Recite and occupy the path, without hindrance, without courtesy.
Kiss me, keep those lips from wandering off
Tell me every sweet and tender thought
Give me all you have to give and more
Fantasies and futures galore
Can you feel the beat, the rhythm, the tune?
Your heart and mine, the countdown
If you feel something coming to you
Believe it and scream it out loud
I don't think I'll miss you anymore
Like I did the day you left
There's so many just like you I could use instead
This passion's burning but only hurts you in the end
This city's gonna swallow the pain
Tomorrow's another today
Night falls at dawn, showtime
Stand for a moment dancing in the moonlight
Till your gaze starts swaying with my body
Keep your eyes on me
ハイ注目 前一丁どーだ
Attention! Front and center, how's this?
宣誓順守 飛ばす
Oath observed, launching...
ホラ一目置いちゃって ホラまだ足りないんじゃないの
Hey, take notice! Hey, isn't it still not enough?
Our night's just begun aimless rest
目は伏せちゃってからの Space
Closing eyes, then Space.
人は無視しちゃってからの Step
Ignoring people, then Step.
乾いた喉潤す オアシス舞い降ります
Moistening the parched throat, an oasis descends.
たまらないんじゃないの
Isn't it irresistible?
Short to the short, My moves bring the sun to the dark
And race, blast a sonic boom, I'd rather feel like I'm surfing jet waves
Don't need the soundblock, I can make it rain as a hands-up-teaser
Baby, get ready, if you wanna ride a wave of OG
ハイ注目 まだ足りないんじゃないの
Attention! Isn't it still not enough?
ダンスは踊ろうか まだまだ足りないの
Shall we dance? It's still not enough.
Our night's just begun aimless rest
開け放て Space
Open up the Space.
エブリバディ
Everybody.
Eyes on me, I can taste the high
Aim high, top high as a fiber, Come here
ハイ注目 前一丁どーだ
Attention! Front and center, how's this?
宣誓順守 飛ばす
Oath observed, launching...
Three, two, one, last time!
ハイ注目 前一丁どーだ
Attention! Front and center, how's this?
宣誓順守 飛ばす
Oath observed, launching...
う〜 抱きしめてる〜
Uhh, I'm hugging you~
行きまーすよ！
Here we go!
無罪！無罪！美少女無罪！
Innocent! Innocent! Pretty girls are innocent!
マリ箱！マリ箱！マリ箱は無罪！
Mari-box! Mari-box! Mari-box is innocent!
...なんて関係ないってさ
...that doesn't matter, you said.
そういう面倒くさいのも含めて愛してくれるって
That you'd love even those troublesome parts of me.
ねえねえ 言ったよね？
Hey, you said it, right?
言ってない？
You didn't?
ふーん、そういうこと言うんだ。
Hmm, so that's what you're saying.
ちなみにこの船では美少女無罪が適用されますけど！
By the way, on this ship, "pretty girls are innocent" applies!
待たせて
Making you wait,
魔法で暴かれ
revealed by magic
行くぞ！
Let's go!
笑顔は君にだけ 特別ですよ！
My smile is only for you, it's special!
私厄介よ
I'm a handful, you know.
港なんかじゃ はしゃげないわ
I can't just frolic at any port.
近頃はね
Not these days.
だから今の私に
So, the current me...
惹かれて欲しい気分
...wants you to be attracted to.
許せません ギリサバ美少女
Unforgivable, borderline-survival pretty girl.
君の一番狙うですよ
I'm aiming for your number one spot.
許されろ 本当は紳士じゃないけど頑張っちゃう
Forgive me, I'm not really a gentleman but I'll try my best.
チュッチュッ チュッチュッ
Chu-chu, chu-chu.
恋する気持ちチュウな中さ
My feelings of love are in the midst of a 'chu'.
てっぺんになっちゃうわ 大人の力
I'll reach the top with adult power.
ドキドキして
My heart is pounding.
まだまだ早い
It's still too early.
Q Q...
わからせてあげるわ
I'll make you understand.
逆らうなら いたい いたい
If you defy me, it'll hurt, it'll hurt.
ご褒美あげましょう
I'll give you a reward.
So back in the city with its only night...
So got you sometimes guess you better give me your life...
わからせてあげるわ
I'll make you understand.
逆らうなら いたい いたい
If you defy me, it'll hurt, it'll hurt.
ご褒美あげましょう
I'll give you a reward.
So back in the city with its only night...
So got you sometimes guess you better give me your life...
ずっと君の隣
Always by your side.
じっと見てるばかり
Just staring intently.
アイアイ止まない雨
Ai ai, the never-ending rain.
世界に二人きり
Just the two of us in this world.
A-M 潜むように心
A-M, as if my heart is lurking.
今この手に取り泣いた
Now taking it in my hands and crying.
痛みさえも愛の形...
Even the pain is a form of love...
運命に 欲張った小指を握る
Gripping the pinky finger that greedily sought destiny.
約束をしよう
Let's make a promise.
Love me, Love me
私しかいらない
I'm the only one you need
Love me, Love me
君がいらない
I don't need you
Love me, Love me
And the next song is...
Sip Some Tea!
Everything was easy,
I did it all alone,
so effortlessly.
I spread my wings
and let my magic unfold.
Got all problems solved
without any setbacks
there is nothing uncontrolled.
But there's no way I can make it,
dream more than I need to win.
I feel how all these things
crumble into little pieces.
I know I gotta soar a little higher,
hope all turns to be the things I desire.
Layaknya burung merak yang bersayap
Like a winged peacock
kan kutaklukkan gelap
I will conquer the darkness
dengan sihir
with magic
angin kan kuajak
I will invite the wind
semua yang terlelap
everyone who is asleep
tuk bangkit
to rise up
melawan dunia.
and fight against the world.
We'll never give up
as long as we got
the strength in ourselves,
we could rise above the pain.
Walking step by step
trusting my own pace
giving me what I deserve to have.
Just believe me let it go,
they'll never bring me down believe me.
Let it go,
it'll never bring us down believe me.
Won't let their cruelty
stealin' my royalty,
and when the universe works against me
I will just...
Let it go
Let it go...
I've been livin' carefree
There's no bitter in the world that could affect me
I spread my wings
And let my magic unfold
Not letting it show
Stings but I'm bigger than my feelings
So that'll be enough
There's no way I can begin
Dream life that I need to win
Fate to feel how all these things
Crumble into little pieces
I know I gotta be better than ever
Hope all turns to be sweeter than ever
Layaknya burung merak yang bersayap
Like a peacock with wings
Kan kutaklukkan gelap
I will conquer the darkness
Dengan sihir angin kan kuajak
With the magic of the wind, I will invite
Semua yang terlelap 'tuk bangkit
All who are asleep to rise up
Melawan dunia
Against the world
As long as we got
The strength in ourselves
We could rise above the pain
We're stronger than them
Walking step by step
Trusting my own pace
Giving me what I deserve to have
Let's go
They'll never bring me down, just believe
They'll never bring us down, just believe
Won't let their cruelty
Stealin' my royalty
And when the universe works against me I will just...
Let it go
Let it go...
PAVOLIA REINE MEMBERSHIP PROMOTIONAL VIDEO "The Royaltea"
Attention please!
Are you somebody looking for a new experience?
Or are you by any chance a MERAKyats...
...who just can't wait for when I'm going to be implementing a certain feature?
Or are you simply wanting to get a head start with flexing...
...using super amazing badges and cute emojis?
Well, you're in luck!
My name is Pavolia Reine,
and I'm going to be here explaining briefly...
...what is going on with Pavolia Reine's membership.
(That is mine, by the way.)
At The Royaltea, our super advanced magical technology...
...grants you badge flexing rights,
which you can constantly show off every time you're here with us.
We also make sure to provide you with utmost care and sense of belonging...
...by granting you a one-of-a-kind experience with cute emojis.
At just the right price, you'll be able to join our exclusive Royaltea parties,
which also means membership-exclusive streams,
in which we can have various talks, play games together,
and do other miscellaneous member involvements.
Like what, you might ask?
Only one way to find out.
And lastly, safety isn't guaranteed, but it is...
...development training in which we aim to build a community...
...of people who like living dangerously.
We welcome everybody with open arms to join The Royaltea.
いいね快晴じゃん
Looking good, clear skies!
ちょっと行きなよ
Go on, head out.
真っ赤な太陽
A crimson sun,
君を知りたーい
I want to know you.
あとはオレ等次第
The rest is up to us.
今日は抱きしめたい
I want to hold you today.
波打ち際の
By the water's edge,
熱い、熱い、決意
a hot, hot determination.
甲子園球児さながらの闘志
Fighting spirit just like a Koshien baseball player.
でも打率は９厘
But my batting average is .009,
オレの十八番
my specialty.
まさに腐れ縁が
Truly, a hard-to-break bond,
繋がれるストーリー
a story being connected.
アッ！
Ah!
1人で遊ぶのは今夜までーい！
Playing alone ends tonight!
上海ハニーと
With Shanghai Honey,
浜辺社交ダンス
beach ballroom dancing.
見つめっぱなし
I can't stop staring,
たまんねぇ女神
at the irresistible goddess.
上海ハニーと
With Shanghai Honey,
エイジアン・ランデヴー
an Asian rendezvous.
寄せては返す
Coming and going,
下心とモラル
ulterior motives and morals.
僕、君のことよく知らないけれど
I don't know you very well, but...
何かトキメいてます
I'm feeling some butterflies.
巧みな話術　彼女を翻弄
Skillful talking, playing with her.
感性本能　くすぐるトーク
Talking that tickles the senses and instincts.
これがオレの理想像
This is my ideal image.
でも現実は理想と　また「離れそう」
But reality and the ideal seem like they'll 'drift apart' again.
で終わりそう
And it looks like it'll end.
いやいや今夜こそは　ゲット！
No, no, tonight for sure, get!
セーシをかけた まさに　ゲット！
Risking it all, truly, get!
今が旬　オレ達の青春
Now is the season, our youth.
「しまっていこう！！」
Let's tighten up!!
気合十分
Full of energy.
上海ハニーと
With Shanghai Honey,
浜辺社交ダンス
beach ballroom dancing.
見つめっぱなし
I can't stop staring,
たまんねぇ女神
at the irresistible goddess.
上海ハニーと
With Shanghai Honey,
エイジアン・ランデヴー
an Asian rendezvous.
寄せては返す
Coming and going,
下心とモラル
ulterior motives and morals.
何か純愛じゃない？　なんてね
Isn't this like pure love? Just kidding.
そっか
I see.
そっか そりゃ無理だよな
So that's how it is, it's impossible.
だってそう
Because that's how it is
僕 きみのことよく知らないけれど
I don't know you well, but
何かトキメいてます
I'm feeling some kind of spark
Sn-sendok, Tante...
Sn-spoon, Auntie...
Campur dibikin sentok
Mixed to make a spoon
A-ampun Tante! Ampun Tante sakit Tante!
M-mercy Auntie! Mercy Auntie it hurts Auntie!
上海ハニーと浜辺社交ダンス
Shanghai Honey and social dancing on the beach
見つめっぱなし たまんねぇ女神
Keep staring, irresistible goddess
上海ハニーとエイジアン・ランデヴー
Shanghai Honey and Asian Rendezvous
寄せては返す 下心とモラル
Coming and going, hidden motives and morals
何か純愛じゃないかもね
Maybe it's not exactly pure love
そっか そりゃそうだよな
So that's how it is, that's right
だってそう
Because that's how it is
僕 きみのことよく知らないけれど
I don't know you well, but
トキメいてます
I'm feeling a spark
Ollie!
Anya!
Reine!
Whoo!
Happy Birthday Reine!
み
Mi
Whew! Ya halo teman-teman, how was it?
Whew! Hello friends, how was it?
いかがだったでしょうか？
How did you like it?
That was performance after performance!
First up, we have the DJ performance. Wow!
For those of you guys who don't know yet,
well, previously I've done a little bit of a 45-minute DJ performance on my channel.
If you guys haven't checked it out, please do check it out.
But you know, some people have been asking, "When is DJ Reine coming back?"
So you know what? I thought this would be the perfect opportunity to include it,
well even though we were on a bit of a time constraint so I had to do something super short.
You know, believe me, it's part of... um, you know, I really, really wanted to include a lot more songs.
It's actually, you know, just a lot of Hololive songs I really, really liked.
I think the songs are like super, super danceable.
And did you notice? You know, we had like Holo-ID songs back to back.
I really, I really, really wanted to make it work, and yeah, it did work.
You know, so, yeah, maybe next time I will do a longer one, you know,
so I can like fwoo fwoo fwoo fwoo put just a lot more songs.
I thought it's just like fun, you know?
I want to share, share and play all the Hololive songs that I like, and maybe in the future I can do more.
And also, you heard my song "Sip Some Tea", but it's a little bit different, right?
The person who did this beautiful remix, thank you so much, Redshift-san!
今回リミックスいただいた方はRedshiftさんです。
The person who provided the remix this time is Redshift-san.
They made it sound really, really cool. Yeah, I really, really like it.
I hope you guys liked it too.
And then my Gen-mates came with me and we sang and performed "Shanghai Honey" together!
I've always wanted to do a super, super, super fun song with Holoro because, you know, it's just a vibe.
It's just a vibe, you know? We're all like super like "woo! yay!"
so I thought "Shanghai Honey" was the perfect fit for the three of us.
Yeah, it was really cool, right? And look at these sunglasses.
Very nice, right?
Well, today's birthday live concert is about to reach the final song.
But before that, I have two announcements to make.
The first announcement is... Birthday Celebration Merch! Ta-da!
There's limited supplies, so get yours ASAP! And here it is!
The merch key visuals are illustrated by Iida Pochi-mama. Yay! So cute, right?
Pochi-mama did the drawing!
And the concept of this merchandise is like, ooh, like neon street performance.
And you see the glowing Tatang too right? With the sunglasses. So cute!
And we can take a look at the items one by one. Let's see the goods. Jeng-jeng, what do we have here?
And we can take a look at the items one by one. Let's see the goods. Ta-da, what do we have here?
Oh my god! What is that? Oh my god! The first one is this! There's a T-shirt! Oh my god!
Look at that oversized T-shirt! Loose-fit T-shirt,
Terbangnya Sang Putri Neon.
Flight of the Neon Princess.
Anjay, keren banget nggak sih?
Man, this is so cool, right?
This is a big silhouette T-shirt that can be worn by everybody.
Kita bisa lihat nggak sih? Can we see?
Can we see? Can we see?
Can we see the zoom-out version of the shirt?
Oh nggak, yang ini udah. Ya udah.
Oh, it's this one already? Okay, never mind then.
Kalau gitu nggak apa-apa.
If that's the case, then that's fine.
And please don't forget to wear it to events, okay?
Pokoknya keren banget. Nanti kalau misalnya... "Hmm, kamu fansnya siapa ya?"
Anyway, it's really cool. So if someone asks, "Hmm, whose fan are you?"
Terus kayak... Sroot! Jreng! "Owalah fansnya Reine," gitu!
Then you go... Sroot! Jreng! "Oh, I'm a Reine fan!" like that.
You can show your oshi through your shirt.
Ya pokoknya keren sih menurut aku ya.
Yeah, anyway, it's cool in my opinion.
And then the next one, ada ini!
And then the next one, we have this!
Ooh, ada apa tuh? Ada tote bag!
Ooh, what's that? A tote bag!
It's a reversible tote bag pakai zipper. Menurut aku keren banget sih.
It's a reversible tote bag with a zipper. I think it's really cool.
It fits A4 size and is designed with a zipper for ease of use.
Jadi kalau misalnya kalian lagi ya, nonton konser lagi hype banget, kayak...
So if you're at a concert and you're getting really hyped, like...
Terus kayak kalian nggak perlu takut barang kalian tumpah semua gitu.
Then you don't need to be afraid your things will all spill out.
Kalau menurut aku sih keren banget. You don't need to be afraid...
I think it's really cool. You don't need to be afraid...
...when you're like super hyped and finally your things fall all over the place...
...because you jump all over the place because you're too hyped.
Yeah, so I think it's very, very perfect with the zipper, of course, gitu.
Yeah, so I think it's very, very perfect with the zipper, of course.
And you can also attach keychains in the tote bag so you can show off.
And you can also attach keychains to the tote bag so you can show off.
And what if you don't have any keychains? What do you do?
Next one we have this! This, this, this!
Aduh capek sendiri aku, heboh sendiri.
Man, I'm getting tired being so hyped by myself.
We have Mark of the Peafowl, Pavolia Reine seru banget cute keychain...
We have Mark of the Peafowl, a very cool and cute keychain...
...featuring aurora fabric and metal charm.
...featuring holographic fabric and a metal charm.
Ini bagus banget karena ada kain hologram dan logamnya gitu ya.
It's really nice because of the holographic fabric and metal.
Jadi kalau misalnya kalian nggak punya atau punya pun nggak apa-apa, pokoknya harus gantungin ini biar pas.
So even if you don't have it, or even if you do, you should hang this to match.
You can hang it like "Shring!" gitu and show off your tote bag and show off your keychain with the shirt.
You can hang it like "Shring!" and show off your tote bag, keychain, and shirt.
Gitu kalau menurut aku sih perfect banget. And then...
I think that's just perfect. And then...
That's not all. There is one more thing. This is the next one!
That's not all! There is one more thing. Next is the next one!
A birthday situational voice pack! Yay!
Keren banget nggak sih? Pokoknya isinya apa? Apa ya? Rahasia deh.
Isn't it so cool? Anyway, what's in it? Well, it's a secret.
Pokoknya it's a secret. You have to listen to know what it's about.
It's a secret, so you have to listen to find out what it's about.
But it will have something to do with this whole performance. Pokoknya keren aja sih menurut aku.
But it will have something to do with this whole performance. I think it's just really cool.
Ya gitu pokoknya keren deh pokoknya.
Anyway, it's cool!
I will zloop! Pokoknya you have to listen. You have to listen.
I will go "zloop"! You definitely have to listen. You have to listen.
You have to listen to find out and tell me what you guys think, okay?
Listen to find out and tell me what you think, okay?
And by the way, this voice pack will be sold separately, not as part of the merchandise set.
By the way, this voice pack will be sold separately, not as part of the merch set.
So please do keep that in mind, okay?
So please keep that in mind, okay?
And also, here's a special bonus you get for buying the goods set.
Also, here's a special bonus for buying the goods set.
Bonus spesial ya buat yang beli yang komplit.
Special bonus for those who buy the complete set.
Ada hand-signed polaroid cheki-style bromide cards. Bromide bergaya polaroid bertanda tangan.
There's a hand-signed polaroid cheki-style bromide card.
Pokoknya everybody will get the card but there's a limited quantity.
Everybody gets a card, but there's a limited quantity.
Jadi ya pokoknya cepet-cepetan aja guys.
So first come, first served, guys!
And if you buy the full set, you will receive a card...
...that can be used in the hololive OFFICIAL CARD GAME as a special bonus.
Pokoknya bisa deh tapi apa namanya... cuma dari ini ya, hololive Official Store gitu, shop.
But it's only available from the hololive Official Store.
Jadi it's a key hololive member card to show off your favorite, namanya oshi holomem card.
It's an "Oshi Holomem Card" to show off your favorite member.
Dan cuma ada di Jepang, bahasa Jepang. Oke?
It's only available in Japan and in Japanese. Okay?
Jadi tapi bisanya belinya dari official shop aja ya guys. So keep that in mind.
But you can buy it from the official shop, so keep that in mind.
hololive official shop only, gitu. And then...
hololive official shop only. And then...
Second announcement! Kita ngebut banget nih guys announcement-nya.
Second announcement! We're rushing through these announcements, guys.
Ayo! Ayo second announcement sekarang sekarang sekarang!
Come on! Come on, second announcement! Right now, right now, right now!
Aku punya lagu baru! Aku punya lagu baru! Pokoknya kalian harus mendengarkan.
I have a new song! I have a new song! You definitely have to listen to it.
Judulnya adalah YUMMY YUM YUMMY.
The title is "YUMMY YUM YUMMY."
Gitu. Jadi lyrics and composition-nya done by Hylen-san.
The lyrics and composition are by Hylen-san.
Pokoknya menurut aku sih keren banget ya. Dan kayaknya tuh feels-nya it's crafted with a dark yet pop feel.
I think it's really cool. It was crafted with a "dark yet pop" feel.
Jadi kalau menurut aku sih kayak mature but also pop gitu. Jadi it's a nice mix of both worlds.
It's mature yet pop at the same time—a nice mix of both worlds.
It will be released on September 10, 00:00. So please be sure to listen to it.
It will be released on September 10, 00:00, so please listen to it.
There might be timezone differences and stuff like that, but yeah please do keep your eyes peeled, okay?
There might be timezone differences, but keep your eyes peeled!
And of course this time we will be ending the live concert with this song, okay?
And of course, we'll be ending this live concert with this song!
So guys, please enjoy, okay? YUMMY YUM YUMMY!
So guys, please enjoy "YUMMY YUM YUMMY!"
Kiite kudasai! Ganti baju dulu! Hehe.
Please listen! I'll go change my clothes first! Hehe.
ヤミ？
Yummy?
ドゥッドゥ
Do-do-do
痛み 痛み Do
Pain, pain, do
ヤミヤミ Do
Yummy, yummy, do
闇病む悩み止み止まない shot
Darkness and worries, the endless shot
サミダレのRainy
Early summer rain
BAM BAM PARTY!
よくばりのStar
Greedy Star
BAM BAM PARTY!
ヤミヤムヤミ
Yummy Yummy Yummy
よくばりのStar
Greedy Star
BAM BAM PARTY!
ヤミヤムヤミ
Yummy Yummy Yummy
BAM BAM PARTY!
フキゲンなLadies
Grumpy Ladies
放心 調子？ なんだって
Absent-minded condition? Whatever it is
徘徊 曖昧 シャットダウン
Wandering, vague, shutdown
月初めのランウェイ 逃げ切るワンダー
Runway at the start of the month, escaping wonder
急成長 正常 難題は
Rapid growth, normal, the difficult problem is
Move in to 選択肢
Moving into options
引っ込んでダーウィンさぁ
Back off, Darwin
Won't you steal my heart
ヤミヤムヤミドゥ ヤミヤムヤミドゥ
Yummy yum yummy do, Yummy yum yummy do
衝動 現実逃避からのエスケープ
Impulse, escaping from reality
SOS なら 燃え上がる前世
If it's an SOS, a burning previous life
欲張りピーポー
Greedy people
Yummy Yummy Justice
One Chance 狙う Jackpot 飲み込むガブ
Aiming for a jackpot in one chance, swallowing it whole
のるかそるか 敗因は ルーティングショー
Sink or swim, the cause of defeat is the routing show
観戦？ 完成？ 貸せ！
Watching? Complete? Hand it over!
お裾分け
Sharing it
ズッキン ズッキン パラッパ
Throbbing, throbbing, parappa
冷めない うちに
While it's still hot
Yummy? ドゥッドゥゥ
Yummy? Du-du-du
病み？ Yummy
Sick? Yummy
ズッキン ズッキン パラッパ
Throbbing, throbbing, parappa
お味は いかが
How does it taste?
Yummy? ドゥッドゥゥ
Yummy? Du-du-du
闇？ Do
Darkness? Do
足りない まだ足りないの
Not enough, it's still not enough
Yummy Yummy Do ドゥッドゥゥ
Yummy yummy do, du-du-du
ラヴィ？ シヴァン
Ravi? Sivan
Lonely Night まだ足りないの？
Lonely Night, is it still not enough?
ビギビギハァ ドゥッドゥゥ
Bigi bigi haa du-du-du
最高臨界点更新中
Updating the maximum critical point
思考のマリアージュ 駆け足ドメスティック
Marriage of thoughts, galloping domestic
右か左か
Right or left
逃げるが勝ちだ
Running away is the victory
暴走中 道中 dug dug
Out of control on the way, dug dug
ガラ空きの Dance Hall
An empty Dance Hall
卵が先だ
The egg comes first
ピースは揃った
The pieces are all here
Sir Baby Baby Baby もう時間がないわ
Sir baby baby baby, there's no more time
Yummy Yummy Yummy Yummy
ラリルラルーリ
Rariru rarūri
捕まえてルルール
Catch the rurūru
壊れる 前に
Before it breaks
ズッキン ズッキン パヤッパ
Throbbing, throbbing, payappa
ルージュを つけて
Putting on rouge
Yummy? ドゥッドゥゥ
Yummy? Du-du-du
病み？ Yummy
Sick? Yummy
ズッキン ズッキン パヤッパ
Throbbing, throbbing, payappa
シンクロリズム
Synchro rhythm
Yummy? ドゥッドゥゥ
Yummy? Du-du-du
闇？ Do
Darkness? Do
Party Time まだ足りないわ
Party Time, it's still not enough
Yummy Yummy Do ドゥッドゥゥ
Yummy yummy do, du-du-du
ラヴィ？ シヴァン
Ravi? Sivan
範囲外 もう消えそうだ
Out of range, I'm about to disappear
ビギビギハァ ドゥッドゥゥ
Bigi bigi haa du-du-du
こっち向いてよ 哀・二重
Look this way, double sorrow
ヤミヤムヤミ
(Yummy Yum Yummy)
Pavolia Reine
September 10 - 00:00 Release!
Yummy Yum Yummy
Pavolia Reine
September 10 - 00:00 Release!
BIRDS NIGHT OUT
- Pavolia Reine Birthday 2024 -